Oh, right...
Doğru...
The full moon turns you minks into those so-called Sulong berserkers.
Minkler, dolunay gecesinde Sulong denilen bir hâle bürünüyor!
Jack!
Jack!
You've gone too far, you damn samurai!
Yapacağınızı yaptınız, samuraylar!
That you even made it here... That's on us!
Buraya kadar sızabilmeniz bizim hatamız!
But you'll never get this close to Kaido again!
Bir daha asla Kaido-san'a yaklaşabileceğinizi düşünmeyin!
You-gara stay back!
Siz-garalar durun!
Jack became our sworn enemy the moment he ravaged our thousand-year-old dukedom.
Jack, bin yıllık düklüğümüzü yerle bir ettiği anda bizim ezeli düşmanımız oldu.
We told him countless times the samurai wasn't there...
Kaç kere samuray falan yok dememize rağmen dinlemedi.
I am that warrior they claimed was not there, Jack!
Onların yok dediği savaşçı işte karşında, Jack!
It was you...!
Demek sendin!
I owe them my life!
Korudukları hayatımı...
I will repay them a hundred times over in this battle!
bu noktada feda etmekten geri durmayacağım!
Wait, Master...
Efendimiz bekleyin...
Please save your strength for Kaido.
Lütfen gücünüzu Kaido'ya saklayın!
You too, Your Grace!
Efendimiz, siz de!
Very well, I leave them to you.
O hâlde size bırakıyorum!
Thank you.
Sağ olun!
In that case, we'll use every bit of our strength to take down Kaido!
Öyleyse gücümün her bir zerresini Kaido'yu alt etmek için kullanacağım!
Stand your ground!
Korkmayın,
Sulong doesn't last long!
Sulong formlarının ömrü kısadır!
Bring it on!
Gelin bakalım,
We're beasts, too!
biz de canavarız!
They've started.
Başladılar.
That blowhard Jack went up there with them?
Jack adisi yukarı mı çıktı?
Unlike you, he knows how to read the room.
Senden farklı o, düşünceli biri.
Huh?!
Heh?!
King... You and I aren't gonna have a problem here...
King, adi herif seni! Bir karın ağrın falan mı var..
are we?!
lan?!
Shinobu?!
Shinobu?!
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Arts!
Olgun-Olgun Baştan Çıkarma Tekniği!
Quietly...
Sessizce...
Oh no!
Eyvah!
Shinobu!
Shinobu!
That was a pretty good plan.
Fikir fena değildi...
However...
ama...
its execution was poor!
uygulamada batırdın!
Shinobu!
Shinobu!
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama...
How shameful to have been rendered unconscious!
Yenilmenin utancı içindeyim!
Let us try again!
Bir kez daha!
What the...?!
O neydi?
What?! He's floating!
Ne?! Havada süzülüyor!
Flying even!
Yani uçuyor!
Too high!
Çok yüksek,
This is terrifying!
korkuyorum!
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama...
What is causing this?!
Neler oluyor?
On behalf of Kaido,
Kaido-san'ın yerine...
I'll see to your execution!
seni ben infaz edeceğim!
What's that?!
O da ne?!
For real, what is that?
Harbiden, o ne?
Sangoro!
Sangoro!
Sanji?!
Sanji-kun?!
Sanji!
Sanji!
You rock!
Süpersin!
Hand over the brat! He must be erased from this world!
Çocuğu geri ver! Bu dünyadan mutlak silinmesi gereken biri o!
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama!
Hey, Momo!
Hey, Momo!
When you shouted out your name...
Az önceki sözlerin...
it gave me the chills!
içime dokundu!
Sangoro...!
Sangoro...!
Shinobu, look after Momo!
Shinobu-chan, Momo sana emanet!
I shall!
Pekâlâ!
Thank you, Sangoro!
Sağ ol, Sangoro!
The Kozuki must be extinguished!
Kozuki ölmeli!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oo, lan, lan!
No good...!
Böyle olmayacak,
I'm in trouble...!
durum kötü!
Cut it out, bird brain!
Yapma, kuş beyinli seni!
At this rate, I'll wind up dead with a hole in my stomach!
Böyle giderse karnımı delecek ve öleceğim!
Just a hole?! I intend to break you in half!
Ne delmesi, seni ikiye ayıracağım!
Where's your little vanishing act?!
Hani nerede şu dandik gizlenme numaran?!
It's only optical camouflage...
Sadece bir tür kamuflaj maalesef.
Just let go of me!
Bırak beni artık!
This is it!
İşin bitti!
Sanji!
Sanji!
That attack was crazy...
Ne fena bir saldırıydı öyle...
Yamabro! Take care of Momo!
Yamao, Momo sende!
Help Shinobu protect him!
Sahinobu'yla birlikte koruyun onu!
What?! Are you sure?!
Heh?! Emin misin?
Of course I'm sure!
Tabii ki eminim!
Right! That actually makes sense...
Haklısın, olması gereken bu!
b-because he's my son!
Ne de olsa o benim oğlum!
Just go!
Hemen git!
Yeah, leave it to me!
Bana bırak!
A father must look after his son!
Babalar evlatlarını kurtarır zaten!
Hey, don't ignore me!
Hey, beni yok sayma!
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
Bekle beni, Momonosuke!
Your father is on his way!
Baban şimdi geliyor!
Wait! Tarry here, I say!
Hey! Dursana be!
I won't let you get away!
Kaçamayacaksın!
All you louts!
Millet,
Let's kill every last samurai raiding this place...
işgale gelen samurayların hepsini gebertin de...
and start the banquet over!
kutlamaya devam edelim!
As for you!
Sana gelince...
The wedding! The tea party! Even this banquet...!
Düğün, çay partisi, şimdi de bu ziyafet!
It takes a special kind of someone to always ruin other people's fun!
Milletin eğlencesini mahvetmekte üstüne yok!
I'll kill you in a way that more than pays for your meddling!
Seni en uygun şekilde öldüreceğim!
You'll die a miserable death!
Son anların acınası olacak!
Hegemony!
Şanlı Ulus!
Crap!
Hass!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Canıma mı kastın be?
What is that hag, a monster?!
Canavar mı lan bu kocakarı?
I heard she's a pirate captain from overseas with as much infamy to her name as Kaido!
Onun da Kaido gibi, adı çıkmış korsanların kaptanı olduğunu duymuştum!
What?! Does that mean we're basically facing two Kaidos?!
Ne?! O hâlde düşmanımız iki Kaido mu demek oluyor?
I wanna go help Momo and Sanji, but she'll just follow me right to them!
Bir an önce, Momo ve Sanji'yi kurtarmaya gitmek istiyorum...
Damn you, Straw Hat...!
Kahrolası Hasır Şapka,
I'm surprised you were able to dodge that!
iyi kaçındın!
Come, Zeus!
Buraya gel, Zeus!
Zeus, what's the hold up?!
Zeus, ne oldu?
Why, you little...!
Sen!
She saw us!
Fark etti!
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's impossible!
Nafile, nafile, nafile, nafile, nafile!
Nami! She'll kill us!
Nami, öldürüleceğiz!
Bad boy!
Kötü çocuk seni!
Come back here!
Haydi, dön bakalım!
O-Okay, Mama...
P-Peki, Mama!
Zeus!
Zeus!
Me or Big Mom!
Ben mi Big Mom mı,
Who do you choose?!
hangimizi seçeceksin?
I can't disobey Mama!
Mama'ya karşı gelemem!
Enough already!
Sıktınız artık!
Naaamiii!
Naaamiii!
You damn Cat Burglar!
Canı çıkasıca Hırsız Kedi seni!
This is all my fault...!
Ben hatalıydım,
Sorry, Mama.
özür dilerim Mama!
I promise not to wander off anymore, so please forgive me!
Bir daha gitmeyeceğim, affet beni!
Oh, so now you're back on my side?
Bak hele, taraf da değiştirirmiş!
How can I trust someone who would follow an annoying tramp like her?!
Onun gibi bir kadının peşinden giden birine kim inanır ki?
What should I do?!
Ne yapmam lazım benim...
How can I earn back your trust?!
güvenini yeniden kazanmam için?
You know what to do.
Belli değil mi?
I need you to kill that bitch.
O kadının hakkından gel!
The watch?
Saat mi?
♪ Threw it away! ♪
♪ Attım gitti! ♪
♪ I'm the wind, baby! ♪
♪ Bana rüzgâr derler! ♪
You already know, right, Zeus?!
Anladın, değil mi Zeus?
If you hold back, you're history!
Elinden geleni yapmazsan silerim seni!
No!
Olamaz!
Soul Sensor: Activate!
Ruh Sensörü: Aktif!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Özür dilerim, Nami!
Rest in peace!
Huzur içinde uyuyasın!
I hate you!
Senden nefret ediyorum!
We are so through!
Tüm ilişkimiz bitti!
Someone help me!
Kurtarın beni!
Wings?
Kanatlar mı?
♪ I will spread them wide! ♪
♪ Genişçe açacağım! ♪
♪ 'Cause I am a bird! ♪
♪ Çünkü ben bir kuşum! ♪
– ♪ Flutter my wings and fly away! ♪
– ♪ Kanat çırpıp uçacağım! ♪
– ♪ High in the sky and on the wind! ♪
– ♪ Gökyüzünde, rüzgârlarla! ♪
♪ I'm Free Rider Franky! ♪
♪ Bana derler, özgür sürücü Franky! ♪
There. You've been cut!
İşte, kılıcımın tadına baktın!
– What?!
– Ne?!
Huh?
Heh?
Oops! I think I ran over something!
Tüh! Bir şeyi ezdim gibi.
Oh well!
Gerçi dert değil...
As long as it wasn't a flower.
bir çiçek değilse eğer.
Big Bro!
Abiciğim!
Mama...!
Mama...!
Mama!
Mama!
Now they've done it!
Bittiniz siz!
They're dead men!
Artık ölüsünüz!
He ran over Big Mom with his bike!
Motoruyla Big Mom'ı ezdi geçti!
Big Bro!
Abiciğim!
Thank you, Franky!
Teşekkür ederim, Franky!
Nami!
Nami!
Are you okay?!
İyi misin?!
Oh, yeah! I'm fabulous!
İyiyim iyiyim çok iyiyim!
With Big Bro here, we're all set!
Abim buradaysa her şey çözülür!
Go! Samurai warriors!
Samuraylarım, saldırın!
Looks like it's started.
Başlamış bile.
Well, well...
Bak hele..
Look who they ran over.
Kocaman bir karmaşa.
Care to partake, Nico Robin?
Bana biraz yardım et, Nico Robin.
Why, I'd be delighted.
Tabii, memnuniyetle.
Nice!
Çok iyi!
Franky and Brook came through as always!
Franky ve Brook'tan beklediğim gibi.
In that case...
O hâlde ben de...
I'll help Kin'emon!
Kin'emon'un olduğu yere...
Here I go!
gidiyorum!
There you are!
Buldum sizi!
You're okay!
Çok şükür iyisiniz!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Who are you?!
Sen de kimsin?
Hey, Shinobu!
Hey, Shinobu!
He's our ally!
O bizim müttefikimiz,
You can trust him!
ona güvenebilirsin!
What? Our ally?!
Ne? Müttefik mi?
It's safer to be with him than to be by yourselves.
Yanınızda olması daha güvenli!
See ya!
Görüşürüz!
Are you truly an ally?
Gerçekten müttefik misin?
Yeah!
Evet!
Very well.
Peki.
I will trust you.
Sana inanıyorum.
Please tell us your name!
İsmin nedir?
– What?!
– Ne?!
I am...
Ben...
I am Kozuki Oden!
Ben Kozuki Oden!
I shall protect you!
Seni koruyacağım!
Father...
Baba...
Lord Oden...
Oden-sama...
Fath... er?
Ba... ba?
Breasts...
Meme...
Horns...!
Boynuz...
You are not my father!
Böyle baba mı olur be?
You are far too suspicious! You are certainly our enemy!
Aşırı şüphe çekici, kesin düşmansın sen!
What?!
Ne?!
Smoke Escape Technique!
Duman Kaçış Tekniği!
Wait!
Bekleyin!
Why are you running away?!
Neden kaçtılar ki?
We're heavily outnumbered.
Sayıları bizden çok fazla,
This will take forever.
sonsuza kadar sürer bu!
You're right!
Sahiden de!
Fighting these underlings is a waste of time!
Bu piyonlarla uğraşmaya değmez!
The dinosaurs of the Soaring Six that Denjiro mentioned...
Denjiro'nun sözünü ettiği Tobi Roppo dinazorlarının...
Should we go take their heads?
kellelerini almaya mı gitsek acaba?
We might be a little outclassed...
Gücümüz yetmeyebilir ama...
but we can at least stall them!
onları oyalayabiliriz!
Really now, I didn't see that coming...
Hayret bir şey, geldiklerini göremedim!
Big Mom's gonna go berserk!
Big Mom delirmek üzere!
Run for it!
Kaçın!
You're popping up one after another...
Bir bir ortaya çıkıyorsunuz...
Straw Hats!
Hasır Şapka tayfası sizi!
Soul King. How nice to see you again.
Ruh Kralı, uzun zaman oldu.
I see your little group is made up of some truly rare creatures!
Sahiden de tayfanızda birçok ender yaratık var.
You have good taste!
Zevklerin güzelmiş!
You like my iron body, you old hag?
Demirden bedenimi sevdin mi, kocakarı seni?
My name is...
Benim adım...
Franky!
Franky!
A bona fide cyborg!
Bir sayborgum!
I'm not just rare, but strong, too!
Ender ve güçlüyüm!
Cut it out, guys!
Durun, ikiniz de!
We need to run! She's an Emperor!
Kaçalım, o bir Yonko!
An Emperor...?
Yonko mu?
We run from those?
Bu yüzden mi kaçmalıyız?
Hey, Nami.
Hey, Nami.
Don't you want...
İstemez misin...
to make our captain...
kaptanımız...
the King of the Pirates?!
Korsanlar Kralı olsun?
Franky...
Franky...
Radical...
Radikal...
Bea–
Işın–
Wha...?!
Şu...
What kind of giant monstrosities...?!
Şu devler de ne böyle?
Hey!
Hey!
You were assigned to a different banquet hall!
Size ayrılan kutlama yeri burası değil!
Numbers!
Numbers!
No!
Hayır!
They're as big as Oars!
Oars kadar büyükler,
What are they?!
nedir bunlar?
It's like Thriller Bark all over again...!
Thriller Bark geldi aklıma!
Are these the guys Kaido bought from Punk Hazard?!
Onlar, Kaido'nun Punk Hazard'dan aldığı...
The failed recreations of the ancient giants?!
antik devlerin başarısız denemeleri demek?!
How lovely...!
Güzel!
In that monster's hand...!
O canavarın elindeki şey...
The Brachio Tank!
Brachio Tankı!
Wasn't Usopp's team in there?!
Usopp'un ekibi!
Hands off the hardware, you overgrown mole!
Bırak o elindekini, koca köstebek seni!
Franky...
Franky...
Radical...
Radikal...
Beam!
Işını!
My laser beam...
Lazer ışınım...
is unstoppable now!
artık durdurulamaz!
Are you sure you didn't want to shoot it this way...
Vurmak istediğin taraf burası değil miydi...
Iron Man?
Demir Adam?
Your arm, if I may!
Kolunu ödünç alıyorum!
Fishman Jujutsu...
Balıkadam Jujutsu...
Mil Fleurs...
Bin Çiçek...
...Whirlpool Shoulder Throw!
...Girdaplı Omuz Fırlatışı!
...Delphinium!
...Hezaren Çiçeği!
Damn you, Jinbe!
Kahrolası, Jinbe!
I remember what you did to my fleet!
Filoma yaptıklarını unutmadım!
I'll kill you, too!
Seni de geberteceğim!
You're welcome to try!
Bana uyar!
How was that?
Nasıldı?
Even better than I expected!
Düşündüğümden de iyiydi!
She'll return angrier than ever!
Daha kızgın dönecektir!
You certainly are a remarkable woman!
Sahiden de korkutucu bir kadınsın!
My bad!
Kusuruma bakmayın...
Thanks for the assist, you two!
ve sağ olun, Jinbe, Robin!
I'm just glad you're unharmed!
İyisin ya yeter!
Now then...
Evet...
It's the moment you've all been waiting for.
şimdi de beklediğiniz an!
Come in, Commander Chopper!
Durum raporu ver, Komutan Chopper!
Usopp!
Usopp!
Wake up! Usopp!
Kendine gel, Usopp!
We got a call from Franky!
Franky'den çağrı aldık!
Hey! You guys are okay, right?!
Hey, siz iyi misiniz?
The Brachio Tank is the world's greatest...
Brachio Tankı dünyanın en...
Do you remember the promise?!
Sözümüzü hatırlıyor musunuz?
The pro... mise...?
Söz mü?
A pirate made of iron...
Demirden yapılan korsan...
the Iron Pirate!
Demir Korsan!
It's docking time!
Haydi birleşelim!
Dock...
Birleş...
...ing?
me mi?
– Docking!
– Birleşme!
Oh, I can see the sky.
Gökyüzünü görebiliyorum.
Okay, I think I can get up from here.
Güzel, buradan çıksam iyi olur.
Don't move!
Kımıldama!
Your Awesomeness!
Queen-sama!
Shut up. I'm on break.
Kes sesini, moladayım.
It's Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka burada!
What?! Straw Hat?!
Ne?! Hasır Şapka mı?
And he isn't alone?!
Başkası da mı varmış?
Hey, Zoro!
Hey, Zoro!
There you are, Luffy!
Luffy sen misin?
Where are you headed?
Nereye gidiyorsun?
Up to where Kaido is!
Kaido'nun yanına!
I'll come with you.
Ben de geliyorum!
As if I would just let you by!
İzin vermem!
What's that giant creature down there?!
Altımızdaki kocaman dev de neyin nesi?
Alright!
Pekâlâ!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Rocket!
Roket!
I can make it!
Güzel, başarabiliriz!
Kaido's up there?
Kaido yukarıda mı?
Yeah! Kin'emon's group is already up there fighting!
Evet, Kin'emon ve diğerleri yukarıda onunla dövüşüyor!
Almost there!
Az kaldı!
Dammit!
Kahretsin!
You bastards are mine, now!
Kaçamayacaksınız, aptallar sizi!
This is as far as you go!
Buradan ileriye gidemeyeceksiniz!
We'll never get up there like this!
Hiçbir açıklık yok!
They've got the sky totally blocked off!
Havada bir sürü uçan düşman var!
Here we go-go-go!
İşte, işte, işte, işte!
Let's do this thing!
Yapıyoruz!
– Docking Formation!
– Birleşme Düzeni!
Black Rhino: Stand By!
Kara Gergedan: Hazır!
– Brachio Head: Change!
– Brachio Kafası: Değiş!
Sorry! This robot is a single-seater.
Kusura bakmayın, bu robot tek kişilik!
What?!
Ne?!
You can't do this!
Bunu yapamazsın!
Those two are...
Şunlar...
Usohachi! Chopperemon!
Usohachi-san ve Chopperemon-san!
You doing okay?!
İyi misiniz?
We can't thank you enough for your sacrifice back at the pleasure hall!
Zevk mekânından sizin sayenizde kurtulmuştuk!
Guys, there are more important things at hand!
Beyler, şimdilik bunu bir kenara bırakalım!
At hand!
Kenara bırakalım!
Feast your eyes on the wonders of docking!
Gözünüz birleşmede olsun!
Feast your eyes!
Olsun!
Iron Pirate...
Demir Korsan...
General Franky!
General Franky!
Here I go!
Başlıyorum!
Franky Cannon!
Franky Topu!
Of course you shot it yourself!
Düşündüğüm gibi, ateşleyici senmişsin!
Of course!
Senmişsin!
Super!
Süper!
Jaki's down!
Jaki'yi hakladılar!
Hey, this is real bad!
Hey, durum kötü!
Let's just get away from here!
Şimdilik buradan çıksak iyi olur!
Good thinking!
Haklısın!
Where's Momo?
Momo...
I guess he got away...
Kaçtı mı acaba?
This suit is annoyingly sturdy...
Bu kıyafet de amma sağlammış!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Kusuruma bakmayın.
This situation kind of tickles my funny bone.
Bu vaziyet beni epey eğlendirdi!
We're still surrounded by enemies.
Hâlâ her yanımız düşman kaynıyor!
But for some reason,
Ama neden bilmem...
I can't imagine losing.
kaybetmeyecekmişiz gibi geliyor.
You're right!
Sahiden de!
Yeah, me neither!
Aynen öyle!
It's strange. Why do we feel this way?
Garip, niye böyle düşünüyorsunuz?
It's obvious, isn't it?!
Belli değil mi?
It's because Sir Straw Hat is with us!
Hasır Şapkalı genç bizle çünkü!
I thought I could get there just by jumping.
Zıplayarak çıkarım sanmıştım.
Damn. Guess it won't be that easy.
Kahretsin, kolay olmayacak.
I'll come with you.
Ben de geliyorum.
Let's just get to the top!
Her hâlükârda çıkmalıyız.
What a pain...
Ne eziyet ama...
Can all these bastards fly?
Hepsi uçabiliyor mu bunların?
Tear off their wings, and they're just caterpillars.
Kanatlarını kopardığımızda sıradan böceklere dönerler.
That's horrific! Your analogies are always so scary!
Düşünce şeklin beni her zamanki gibi korkutuyor!
So these are the Superstars we've heard so much about.
Herkesin konuştuğu Önderler şunlar demek.
They may look tough, but they don't hold a candle to our captain!
Güçlü görünseler de bizim kaptanımız daha güçlü!
Yeah!
Evet!
It's my duty as a navigator to get the captain to his destination!
Kaptanı, gitmek istediği yere götürmek rotacı olarak bana düşer.
Super count on me!
Süper, bana bırakın!
Let the General Franky clear the way for you!
General Franky yolu sizin için açacaktır!
Let's go, Captain!
Gidelim, Kaptan!
Yeah! One more time! Ready?!
Evet! Bir kez daha, gidiyoruz!
Everyone! I'll leave the rest to you!
Millet, gerisini size bırakıyorum!
Back us up!
Bize destek olun!
I'm gonna go...
Ben Kaido'yu...
kick Kaido's ass!
mahvetmeye gidiyorum!